[{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980440218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":6695,"timeElapsed":263213},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444565,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":4346,"timeElapsed":267560},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980448468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3901,"timeElapsed":271463},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980452065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3596,"timeElapsed":275060},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980454741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2675,"timeElapsed":277736},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980460833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":6091,"timeElapsed":283828},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468903,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":8069,"timeElapsed":291898},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980477544,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":8639,"timeElapsed":300539},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980484607,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7064,"timeElapsed":307602},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980494661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":8720,"timeElapsed":317656},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980504276,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":9613,"timeElapsed":327271},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980508774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4497,"timeElapsed":331769},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980511057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2282,"timeElapsed":334052},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980513107,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2049,"timeElapsed":336102},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980517949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4839,"timeElapsed":340943},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980520934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2984,"timeElapsed":343929},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980526025,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":5091,"timeElapsed":349020},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980528631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2605,"timeElapsed":351626},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980538737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":8948,"timeElapsed":361732},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980542376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3638,"timeElapsed":365371},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980546354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3978,"timeElapsed":369349},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980550862,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4506,"timeElapsed":373857},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980552794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":1931,"timeElapsed":375789},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980555358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2564,"timeElapsed":378352},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980557047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1689,"timeElapsed":380042},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980560816,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3768,"timeElapsed":383811},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980569171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":8355,"timeElapsed":392166},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980578011,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":7643,"timeElapsed":401006},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980581932,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3919,"timeElapsed":404927},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980584496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2562,"timeElapsed":407491},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980587060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2563,"timeElapsed":410055},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980589005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":1946,"timeElapsed":412000},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980591018,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2011,"timeElapsed":414013},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980592933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1915,"timeElapsed":415928},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980595952,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3018,"timeElapsed":418947},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980597553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1601,"timeElapsed":420548},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980608319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9668,"timeElapsed":431314},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980610620,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2300,"timeElapsed":433615},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980613255,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2635,"timeElapsed":436250},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980615432,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2175,"timeElapsed":438427},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980617720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2286,"timeElapsed":440715},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980620024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2303,"timeElapsed":443019},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980624512,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4488,"timeElapsed":447507},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980625868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1355,"timeElapsed":448863},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980627384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1515,"timeElapsed":450378},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980632745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":4345,"timeElapsed":455740},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980634820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2073,"timeElapsed":457815},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980637252,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2431,"timeElapsed":460247},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980639370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2117,"timeElapsed":462365},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980641237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1867,"timeElapsed":464232},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980643340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2100,"timeElapsed":466335},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980644966,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1626,"timeElapsed":467961},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980646664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1697,"timeElapsed":469659},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980648893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2229,"timeElapsed":471888},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980655423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":5705,"timeElapsed":478418},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980656910,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1486,"timeElapsed":479905},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980660408,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3498,"timeElapsed":483403},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980663262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2853,"timeElapsed":486257},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980665156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":1894,"timeElapsed":488151},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980666774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1617,"timeElapsed":489769},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980670024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3248,"timeElapsed":493019},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980672376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2350,"timeElapsed":495371},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980674316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1939,"timeElapsed":497311},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980683782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8354,"timeElapsed":506777},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980686354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2571,"timeElapsed":509349},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980689091,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2737,"timeElapsed":512086},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980691674,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2581,"timeElapsed":514669},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980694454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2779,"timeElapsed":517449},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980697233,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":2779,"timeElapsed":520228},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980698996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":1762,"timeElapsed":521991},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980700706,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1710,"timeElapsed":523700},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980710073,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9368,"timeElapsed":533068},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980716275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6200,"timeElapsed":539270},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980726292,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":8896,"timeElapsed":549287},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980727712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1419,"timeElapsed":550707},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980731385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3672,"timeElapsed":554380},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980733558,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2172,"timeElapsed":556553},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980737726,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4167,"timeElapsed":560721},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980740848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3121,"timeElapsed":563843},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980743120,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2271,"timeElapsed":566115},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980745834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2712,"timeElapsed":568829},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980747440,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":1606,"timeElapsed":570435},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980749316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1876,"timeElapsed":572311},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980754114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3733,"timeElapsed":577109},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980757414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3299,"timeElapsed":580409},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980759617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2201,"timeElapsed":582612},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980761454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1837,"timeElapsed":584449},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980764262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2807,"timeElapsed":587257},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980767282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3019,"timeElapsed":590277},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980769116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1833,"timeElapsed":592111},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980770847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":1731,"timeElapsed":593842},{"subjectID":"b7k4qsqalp","prolificID":"660c3df9986b3c273c28bdb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2489ce3c03f47ebbb5d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980773102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2253,"timeElapsed":596097}]